allexperts.com 2013-05-21

# AllExperts - Privacy Policy

## The Short Version

AllExperts.com will never share, rent, or sell your personal information without your consent, **unless it is required by law**.

When AllExperts.com sends newsletters to subscribers it may allow Advertisers or Partners to include messages in those newsletters but those Advertisers or Partners will never have access to your personal information including your email address. All newsletters will come directly from AllExperts.com. At any time a user may unsubscribe from a newsletter.

## The Fine Print

**Tracking on AllExperts.com**  
AllExperts.com will use cookies, pixel trackers, server logs, and any Internet technology in order to measure the effectiveness of the AllExperts.com service and any Advertising campaigns as well as to target meaningful content and Ads to our users.

**Your Ad Choices and Tracking by Third-Parties**  
AllExperts.com uses DoubleClick, Google, and other third-party Ad Servers to serve and display Advertisements on AllExperts.com. AllExperts.com does not provide personally identifiable information to Ad Servers. These Ad Servers and Advertisers may use cookies, pixel trackers, or other internet technology to improve the effectiveness and targeting of Advertisements to you within AllExperts.com and any other place where that third-party is serving Advertisements. AllExperts.com does not have access to, nor control over, advertisers' or ad service providers' cookies or how they may be used or how they were collected. In many cases, this information could be used to show you ads based on your interests on other Web sites.

You have options and choices about the collection and use of information by third-parties on our site:

  1. For more information about these third-party Ad Networks and opting out of tracking, see:  
<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

  2. For more information about interest-based information tracking and opting out, see:  
<http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>

  3. For information about disabling and controlling third-party cookies in your browser, see:  
<http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=1>

## Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please visit us at:

Or you can contact us by mail at:

_Customer Care  
About.com, Inc.  
249 West 17th Street  
New York, NY 10011_

_Updated January 2011_
